louderthanlifefestival.com 2018-01-28

# Thank you for visiting Danny Winner Presents (“DWP”). Because your privacy is important to us, we provide this Privacy Policy explaining our online practices and your choices regarding our use of information about you collected through our online and mobile Web sites, services, and applications (“Site” or “Sites”). This Policy applies only to the information collected from the users of our Sites and does not apply to any information collected offline at festivals.

                                Danny Wimmer Presents Privacy Policy
        	  
Thank you for visiting Danny Winner Presents (“DWP”). Because your privacy is important to us, we
provide this Privacy Policy explaining our online practices and your choices regarding our use of
information about you collected through our online and mobile Web sites, services, and applications
(“Site” or “Sites”). This Policy applies only to the information collected from the users of our Sites and
does not apply to any information collected offline at festivals.
   Information We Collect
Registration,
   	           Social Media, and Other Information. To enable you to participate in our Site
offerings and fulfill your requests for information regarding our events, products, and offerings, we
may collect certain personally identifiable information, including contact information such as name,
address, telephone number, and e-mail address. We also may collect information about your interest
in and use of our events, products, and offerings. If you connect to our Sites or sign up for promotions
using your Facebook credentials, you authorize us to collect your authentication information, such as
your username, access credentials, and other information that may be available through your
Facebook account, including your name, profile picture, country, hometown, e-mail address, date of
birth, and gender.
If you post information or content, such as by posting photos, commenting on a blog, or participating
in online forums or communities at our Sites, or when you interact with our Sites through social media
sites, plug-ins or other applications, depending on your privacy settings, this information may become
public on the Internet. Therefore, we cannot prevent further use of this information. You can control
what data you share through privacy settings available on some social media sites. For more
information about how you can customize your privacy settings and how third party social media sites
handle your personally identifiable information, please refer to their privacy help guides, privacy
policies and terms of use.
Technical and Usage Information. We also collect certain non-personally identifiable information
when you use our Sites such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Firefox, Internet Explorer),
the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows, Mac OS, iOS, and Android), the domain
name of your Internet service provider or mobile carrier, IP address, and certain usage information.
Information from Mobile Devices. If you access our Sites on your mobile telephone or other
mobile device, we also may collect your unique device identifier and mobile device IP address (e.g.
MAC address), as well as information about your device’s operating system, mobile carrier, and
mobile Internet browsers, your precise location information, and other information described in this
Policy.
Information from Other Sources. We may, on occasion, combine information we receive online
with outside records and use such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, such as to
enhance our ability to market to you events, offerings, and products that may be of interest to you.
   How We Use Information
Registration
   	           and Account Information. We use information you provide to fulfill your requests for
our events and offerings (e.g., send you the information about events, subscribe to our newsletters,
participate in one of our contests or promotions), respond to your questions, improve Site content, and
to offer you other products, programs or events that we believe may be of interest to you. We also

may use personally identifiable information to contact you regarding your use of our offerings or
events, changes to our Privacy Policy, Terms of Use, or other policies or terms that affect you and use
of our Web Site or our offerings. In addition, we may use such information to improve the content and
navigation of our Sites, or for other internal purposes.
Use of Mobile Device Data. When you access our Sites on a mobile device, we may use the
information collected for any of the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy. For example, we use
information collected on mobile devices to enable you to do things like (i) watch video clips, (ii) get
event news and updates, (iii) locate and access personalized information or functionality based on
your location (e.g., find events near you, tag photographs, or check in to a certain venue), and (iv)
follow blogs. We may also use this information to offer you products, programs and events we believe
may be of interest to you and otherwise tailor your experience.
   What Information We Share
Our	   Affiliates. We may disclose personally identifiable to our corporate subsidiaries or entities
affiliated with DWP. Any personally identifiable information provided to DWP’s subsidiaries or entities
affiliated with DWP will be treated by those subsidiaries and affiliated entities in accordance with the
terms of this Privacy Policy.
Agents and Contractors. We may use the services of agents and contractors to assist us in
providing our offerings, products and events.
Brand Partners. We may, from time to time, share personally identifiable information with unrelated
third parties (e.g., other marketers/brand partners) to enable them to provide users with opportunities
to learn of products or events in which they may be interested. Please see the "Your Choices" section
below for more information on how you can express your preferences regarding our sharing of
information.
Legal and Law Enforcement. We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to
legal process (e.g., a court order or a subpoena) or comply with legal requirements. We also may
disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request or where we believe it is
necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations
involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as
otherwise required or permitted by law.
Change of Control. We may transfer information about you in the event of a business transaction,
such as if we or one of our business units or our relevant assets are acquired by, sold to, or merged
with another company.
Aggregate Data. We may disclose anonymous, aggregated user statistics to third parties for a
variety of purposes. For example, we may disclose how many individuals visited certain areas of our
Sites, how many men or women sign up to a particular product, or other demographic data about
users of our offerings.
  Your Choices
  	  
Marketing       Communications. As noted above, we may use the personally identifiable information we
collect from you to offer you products, opportunities, and events that may be of interest to you. If you
would like to opt out of future promotional materials from us, you may indicate this preference by
following the unsubscribe instructions at the end of e-mail communications or by contacting us at

communityinfo@dannywimmerpresents.com. Please note that even if you opt out of promotional
messages from us, we will continue to send you important account-related information.
As also noted above, we may, from time to time, share personally identifiable information with
companies whose practices are not covered by this privacy notice (e.g., brand partners/other
marketers) that want to market products or services to you. If you would like to request that we not
share your information for such purposes, please send us an e-mail at
communityinfo@dannywimmerpresents.com.
Mobile. If you no longer wish to have any information collected by the Site, you may uninstall the
application by using the standard uninstall processes available on your mobile device or via the
mobile application marketplace or network.
CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS - YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
If you are a California resident, you can request information about our practices related to disclosing
your personal information to certain third parties and/or opt-out of our sharing of your information with
unaffiliated third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Please send your request
(along with your full name, e-mail address, postal address, and the subject line labeled “Your
California Privacy Rights”) by e-mail at communityinfo@dannywimmerpresents.com.
  Cookies, Beacons and Do Not Track
  	  
Cookies. To enhance your experience with our Sites, our Web pages may use "cookies." Cookies
are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences.
We use cookies to understand Site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our Site[s]. For
example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our Web pages (e.g., to recognize
you by name when you return to our Site), save your password in password-protected areas, and
enable you to use shopping carts on our Site[s]. We also may use cookies to offer you products,
programs, or services. You can adjust your browser to reject cookies from us or from any other Web
site.
Some of our Sites may use locally stored objects (sometimes referred to as "Flash cookies") to
provide certain content, such as video clips. Adobe's Flash player and similar applications use this
technology to remember settings, preferences, and usage similar to browser cookies. Flash cookies
are not managed through your web browser, but you can access your Flash management tools
from Adobe's web site. [This text should be hyperlink to
http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.
html
Web Beacons. We may also use "Web beacons" or similar technologies that monitor your use of our
Sites. Web beacons (or Web bugs) are small strings of code that enable delivery of a graphic image
on a Web page for the purpose of transferring data, such as the IP (Internet Protocol) address of the
computer that downloaded the page on which the Web beacon appears, the URL (Uniform Resource
Locator) of the page on which the Web beacon appears, the time the page containing the Web
beacon was viewed, the types of browser that fetched the Web beacon and the identification number
of any cookie on the computer previously placed by that server.
When corresponding with you via HTML capable email, Web beacons and similar technologies let us
know whether you received and opened our email.

 Do Not Track. We do not currently take actions to respond to Do Not Track signals because a
uniform technological standard has not yet been developed. We continue to review new technologies
and may adopt a standard once one is created.
 Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Links
 	  
From       time to time, we may offer content (e.g., promotions) that is sponsored by or co-branded with an
identified third party (e.g., brand partners). In these instances, the third party may obtain information
that you voluntarily submit to participate in a Site activity. We have no control over the third party’s
use of this information.
Our Site also may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours.
You should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is
submitted
to, or collected by, these third parties.
 Data Security
 	  
We have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information
that we have collected from you at our Sites.
Updates
 Updates
From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you of material changes to our
Privacy Policy by placing a notice on our Site or contacting you with the email address we have in our
records. Please check back to this policy statement at our Sites to learn what information we collect,
how we use it, and to whom we share it.
      Updating Your Information and Contacting Us
      	  
You can always contact us for any reason regarding or privacy practices or in order to (1) delete your
personally identifiable information from our systems, (2) update the personally identifiable information
that you have provided to us, and (3) change your preferences with respect to marketing contacts or
other activities. To do so, simply email us at communityinfo@dannywimmerpresents.com.
Effective Date: This Policy is effective as of May 21, 2015.
